rightbiz.co.uk 2015-04-07

# Privacy Policy - RightBiz UK

RightBiz takes everyone's privacy very serious. 

Protecting your privacy is one of our highest priorities. We developed this policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protect your privacy. Please read the following information to learn more about our privacy policy.

We are serious about guarding and protecting the security of your personal information and the details of any transactions that may be made on our website.

We collect personal information from you when you register or provide it and in some cases, from third party sources.

We will not give, share or sell your personal information to third parties, advertisers or any other forms of internet activities, unless required to by law regulations.

Your billing information is a sensitive piece of information, we use a secure server. Any information you give us is encrypted using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) and stored in a secure operating environment, please be sure to keep this information safe and do not share with others. 

We are not responsible or liable for the privacy issues of any outside websites we may be linking directly to, so we urge you to be careful when you enter any personal information outside our site.

We also use information in aggregate form so that no individual user is identified to monitor the traffic of visitors and to provide statistics to our advertisers.

Like most web servers, our server automatically records activity on our site. Among other things, this allows us to find and fix web site problems. Your IP address is automatically logged by our servers for systems administration purposes. Your IP address does not hold any personal identifiable information.

We use cookies and we will attempt to limit the use of cookies as much as possible. We do not use cookies to see what other information is stored on your computer or attempt to access personal information about you.

If you do not want a cookie to be created on your computer's web browser, please disable them on your settings but bear in mind that some services may not function correctly if you choose to disable them.

We welcome users of all ages to our content and services. If you are under the age of 12, we specifically request that you have the permission of your parents or legal guardian to view any content.

We will not be held responsible for any information received or disclosed by our users and third parties.

If you have any complaints relating to our privacy policy, you can contact us using the contact form, we will carefully investigate all complaints.
